<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroMonth</string>
    <string name='title0'>Getting Started with Android</string>
    <string name='title1'>Creating User Interfaces in Android</string>
    <string name='title2'>Understanding Activities and Intents</string>
    <string name='title3'>Exploring Views and Widgets in Android</string>
    <string name='title4'>Managing Resources and Assets</string>
    <string name='title5'>Handling User Input in Android</string>
    <string name='title6'>Testing and Debugging Android Apps</string>
    <string name='title7'>Using Fragments for UI Navigation</string>
    <string name='title8'>Building Dynamic Lists with RecyclerView</string>
    <string name='title9'>Data Storage in Android</string>
    <string name='title10'>Implementing Notifications and Permissions</string>
    <string name='title11'>Networking and API Integration</string>
    <string name='title12'>Working with Multimedia and Camera</string>
    <string name='title13'>Integrating Location and Maps</string>
    <string name='title14'>Background Tasks and Services in Android</string>
    <string name='title15'>Introduction to Android Architecture Components</string>
    <string name='title16'>Implementing Material Design in Android</string>
    <string name='title17'>Optimizing Performance in Android Apps</string>
    <string name='title18'>Enhancing Security and Privacy in Android</string>
    <string name='title19'>Publishing and Distributing Android Apps</string>
    <string name='title20'>Brainstorming Your Android Project</string>
    <string name='title21'>Setting Up Your Project and Creating Basic UI</string>
    <string name='title22'>Implementing Core Functionality of Your App</string>
    <string name='title23'>Managing Data and Implementing Persistence</string>
    <string name='title24'>Adding User Authentication to Your App</string>
    <string name='title25'>Polishing the User Interface of Your App</string>
    <string name='title26'>Implementing Advanced Features and Functionality</string>
    <string name='title27'>Testing and Debugging Your App</string>
    <string name='title28'>Optimizing Performance and Refining Your App</string>
    <string name='title29'>Finalizing Your App and Preparing for Deployment</string>
    <string name='desc0'>Learn the basics of Android, set up the development environment, and understand the fundamentals.</string>
    <string name='desc1'>Dive into XML layout files, explore various UI components, and learn how to design appealing interfaces for your Android app.</string>
    <string name='desc2'>Learn about the core building blocks of Android apps, activities, and intents. Understand how to navigate between screens and pass data.</string>
    <string name='desc3'>Explore different views and widgets available in Android, such as buttons, text fields, lists, and more. Learn how to interact with them.</string>
    <string name='desc4'>Understand how to use resources effectively in Android apps, including images, strings, colors, and other assets.</string>
    <string name='desc5'>Learn how to handle various user input events like button clicks, text input, gestures, and implement interactive features.</string>
    <string name='desc6'>Explore various testing techniques and tools available in Android, and learn how to debug your app effectively.</string>
    <string name='desc7'>Dive into fragments, a flexible UI component, and learn how to navigate between different fragments within your app.</string>
    <string name='desc8'>Learn how to create dynamic lists using RecyclerView and adapters. Implement efficient and interactive list-based UIs.</string>
    <string name='desc9'>Learn about different storage options in Android, including SharedPreferences, files, and databases. Understand how to save and retrieve data.</string>
    <string name='desc10'>Understand how to display notifications to users and handle user permissions in Android apps.</string>
    <string name='desc11'>Dive into networking concepts and learn how to make HTTP requests, parse JSON responses, and integrate APIs into your Android app.</string>
    <string name='desc12'>Understand how to capture photos/videos, play audio/video, and work with the device\'s camera in your Android app.</string>
    <string name='desc13'>Learn how to access the device\'s location, display it on a map, and integrate location-based features into your app.</string>
    <string name='desc14'>Explore techniques for performing tasks in the background and creating services for long-running operations.</string>
    <string name='desc15'>Explore the Android Architecture Components, including ViewModel, LiveData, Room, and learn how to build robust and maintainable apps.</string>
    <string name='desc16'>Understand the principles and guidelines of Material Design and learn how to apply them to create visually appealing apps.</string>
    <string name='desc17'>Understand performance optimization techniques, including memory management, background tasks, and UI responsiveness.</string>
    <string name='desc18'>Learn about best practices for securing your Android app and protecting user data from unauthorized access.</string>
    <string name='desc19'>Get familiar with the app publishing process, create a signed APK, and learn how to distribute your app on the Google Play Store.</string>
    <string name='desc20'>Spend this day coming up with a project idea that interests you. Plan out the features, user interface, and functionality of your app.</string>
    <string name='desc21'>Create a new Android project, set up necessary dependencies, and start building the basic user interface of your app.</string>
    <string name='desc22'>Begin implementing the core features of your app, such as data retrieval, user interactions, and any specific functionalities unique to your project.</string>
    <string name='desc23'>Set up data management for your app, including storing and retrieving data from a local database or remote server.</string>
    <string name='desc24'>Implement user authentication features, such as user registration, login, and secure session management, if relevant to your project.</string>
    <string name='desc25'>Focus on refining the user interface of your app, ensuring a smooth and intuitive user experience. Pay attention to layout, colors, typography, and usability.</string>
    <string name='desc26'>Work on incorporating any advanced features into your app, such as real-time updates, notifications, location-based services, or integrations with external APIs.</string>
    <string name='desc27'>Conduct thorough testing of your app, including functional testing, UI testing, and fixing any bugs or issues that arise during the testing phase.</string>
    <string name='desc28'>Analyze and optimize your app\'s performance, including reducing memory usage, optimizing database queries, and improving overall responsiveness.</string>
    <string name='desc29'>Complete any remaining tasks, such as adding app icons, preparing promotional materials, and creating a signed APK. Deploy your app to the Google Play Store or any other distribution platform.</string>
    <string name="expand_button">Expand Button to view description of each day</string>
    <string name="days_30">30 Days of</string>
    <string name="made">Made with</string>
    <string name="jetpack">JetPack Compose</string>
    <string name="jetpack_link">https://developer.android.com/jetpack/compose</string>
    <string name="images_by">Images by</string>
    <string name="name">kjparegkar</string>
    <string name="image_link">https://www.freepik.com/author/kjpargeter</string>
</resources>